tablotv.com 2018-09-06

# Tablo Privacy Policy | Over The Air (OTA) DVR | Tablo

Nuvyyo respects your right to privacy. During your visit to our website, your privacy is respected. We do not collection personal information about you unless you opt to complete forms or applications that request necessary personal information. We recognize the need to ensure the appropriate protection and management of any information that you may provide us while you are visiting our website. This following text outlines the steps that we have taken to ensure your privacy.

**Information Collection**  
You may generally visit the Nuvyyo/Tablo website anonymously, without revealing who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.

We also provide the resources for you to register with us, where you may voluntarily provide personal details, in order to request further information, to keep in contact with us, to apply for career opportunities, or to provide feedback. Where appropriate, we may contact you to respond to your request or to keep in contact with you. You may also enter our website as a registered visitor to gain access to resources including proprietary information, special tools, customer service, or support. Personal information collected through this website is provided only to our office personnel who require the information. We will use the personal information collected for the stated purposes only.

From time to time, we may track Internet address domain information from our website visitors which is used to provide aggregate trending information and statistics. This trending information is intended to help us improve our website and to help our systems administrators diagnose any potential difficulties or to ensure quality service.

**Cookies**  
Our Customer Support Web Site uses "cookies" so that we can better serve you with more tailored information when you return to our Web Site. Cookies are pieces of information that retain user ID and password information that are stored on your hard drive. The information stored will make your usage of our Web Site easier and faster because it allows you to use the Web Site without having to re-enter information on each visit.

Nuvyyo does not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in the cookie, and we do not use information transferred through cookies for any purposes. This information is not shared or sold to any third parties whatsoever.

**Information Use**  
We will not release any data that you have provided, as part of the registration or information request process, in a personally identifiable form to any 3rd party organizations. Nuvyyo may, where appropriate, engage 3rd party organizations for services where this personally identifiable information may be shared. In these circumstances, all data will be covered under contract and legally binding confidentially agreements.

We will disclose requisite information to judicial or governmental authorities if required to do so by law or court order.

**Updating or Removal of Information**  
At any time, you may choose to modify, view, or remove any and all personal information that you have provided.

To remove your personal information from our database, please use our [contact form](http://www.tablotv.com/contact) to email us advising us of your request.

At any time, you may view the information that you have provided us. You may request changes to this information where you deem appropriate. Please use our contact form or contact us directly at 613-454-5675 advising us of your request.

**Security of Information**  
Nuvyyo uses security technology including authentication, encryption and authorization to safeguard your data.

Please note that email messages are not transmitted in a secure form and hence are susceptible to unauthorized reading or interception.

**Links to Other Websites**  
For the convenience of our visitors, Nuvyyo/Tablo's website contains links to other sites. We do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content nor the privacy policies, where present, for those sites.

Nuvyyo reserves the right to modify this privacy document at any time. Any changes will be promptly updated on this website.
